[
    {
        "index": 0,
        "number": 1,
        "question": "What is the capital of the Austria?",
        "choices": ["Paris", "Vienna", "Prague", "Venice"],
        "answer": "Vienna"
        },
    {
        "index": 1,
        "number": 2,
        "question": "Where is Bern the capital of?",
        "choices": ["Germany", "Belgium", "Croatia", "Switzerland"],
        "answer": "Switzerland"
        },
    {
        "index": 2,
        "number": 3,
        "question": "Where is Nova Scotia?",
        "choices": ["Usa", "Uk", "Canada", "Australia"],
        "answer": "Canada"
        },
    {
        "index": 3,
        "number": 4,
        "question": "What US state is Atlanta located in?",
        "choices": ["Alabama", "Arkansas", "Georgia", "Louisiana"],
        "answer": "Georgia"
        },
    {
        "index": 4,
        "number": 5,
        "question": "Which city is the capital of Hungary?",
        "choices": ["Budapest", "Bucharest", "Sofia", "Minsk"],
        "answer": "Budapest"
        },
    {
        "index": 5,
        "number": 6,
        "question": "How many litres of water does it take to make one egg?",
        "choices": ["10", "56", "144", "200"],
        "answer": "200"
        },
    {
        "index": 6,
        "number": 7,
        "question": "How many tons of carbon are absorbed by 1 tree in its lifetime?",
        "choices": ["1", "3", "6", "10"],
        "answer": "1"
        },
    {
        "index": 7,
        "number": 8,
        "question": "How many calories on average are in a Big Mac?",
        "choices": ["240", "410", "560", "755"],
        "answer": "560"
        },
    {
        "index": 8,
        "number": 9,
        "question": "How many calories on average does 30 minutes of running burn?",
        "choices": ["295", "345", "470", "520"],
        "answer": "295"
        },
    {
        "index": 9,
        "number": 10,
        "question": "How much caffeine is a large coffee shop coffee in 'mg'?",
        "choices": ["90", "130", "240", "300"],
        "answer": "240"
        },
    {
        "index": 10,
        "number": 11,
        "question": "What cocktail do you get if you mix cranberry, orange liqueur and vodka?",
        "choices": ["Cosmopolitan", "Margarita", "Screwdriver", "Daiquiri"],
        "answer": "Cosmopolitan"
        
        },
    {
        "index": 11,
        "number": 12,
        "question": "What salad dressing do you get if you mix buttermilk, cottage cheese, chives, garlic and parmesan?",
        "choices": ["Vinaigrette", "Caesar", "Catalina", "Ranch"],
        "answer": "Ranch"
        },
    {
        "index": 12,
        "number": 13,
        "question": "What is the main ingredient in a White Russian?",
        "choices": ["Vodka", "Whiskey", "Tequila", "Brandy"],
        "answer": "Vodka"
        },
    {
        "index": 13,
        "number": 14,
        "question": "What word is missing from this famous cult movie quote 'They call it a *blank* with cheese.'?",
        "choices": ["Burger", "Whopper", "Royale", "Patty"],
        "answer": "Royale"
        
        },
    {
        "index": 14,
        "number": 15,
        "question": "How much did Avenger: Infinity War make on opening night to the closest million $s?",
        "choices": ["110", "143", "257", "312"],
        "answer": "257"
        },
    {
        "index": 15,
        "number": 16,
        "question": "What word is missing from this famous movie quote 'I love the smell of *blank* in the morning.'?",
        "choices": ["Coffee", "Doughnuts", "Napalm", "Smoke"],
        "answer": "Napalm"
        },
    {
        "index": 16,
        "number": 17,
        "question": "What specific creature does Indiana Jones hate?",
        "choices": ["Scorpions", "Snakes", "Spiders", "Cockroaches"],
        "answer": "Snakes"
        },
    {
        "index": 17,
        "number": 18,
        "question": "What year was Gladiator first released?",
        "choices": ["1998", "2000", "2001", "2003"],
        "answer": "2000"
        },
    {
        "index": 18,
        "number": 19,
        "question": "What bird is associated with Han Solo’s “Millenium” ship?",
        "choices": ["Eagle", "Sparrow", "Hawk", "Falcon"],
        "answer": "Falcon"
        },
    {
        "index": 19,
        "number": 20,
        "question": "Who is the Brown Wizard from the Hobbit?",
        "choices": ["Beorn", "Radagast", "Thranduil", "Mithrandir"],
        "answer": "Radagast"
        }
        ]